翻译/压制：女番L
严禁其他组织或个人用于商业用途
翻译仅出于兴趣 若有不严谨或者纰漏之处 欢迎在评论指正
Oh..
Oh.
妈，我回家都五秒啦，你还在做饭
Mom, l'm home five seconds,you're already cooking.
快来，我要给你看个东西
Come here, l got something to show you.
好吧，等等 -到外面来
-Well, wait a minute. -Outside.
等一下
Wait a minute.
我还没给你做完饭呢
l haven't finished cooking your dinner.
好啦，是个惊喜，没关系啦
Yeah, it's a surprise.lt's all right.
拜托 来吧
Come on.
闭上眼睛
Shut your eyes.
好 闭上
Good. Shut 'em.
准备好了吗 -嗯
-Okay, you ready? -Mm-hmm.
你确定？-嗯嗯
-You sure? -Mm-hmm.
好吧
All right.
转身
Whoa. Turning.
哦好冷
Oh, it's cold.
才不冷呢
lt's not cold.
连小鸡都很冷
Even the chickens are cold.
好 台阶 注意台阶
Okay, steps.We have steps.
好了吗 一
-Ready? One...
一
-One...
二
-...two...
三
-...and three.
-...three!
好 看吧
Okay, look.
不，不是那个
-No, that's not it. -Well...
闭眼 闭眼 这边
Shut 'em. Shut 'em.Come on.
弗兰克...
Now, Frank...
还 还要多远啊 喔
h-how far are we gonna go? Ooh.
这边 这边 这边...
Come on, come on. Come on...
没关系啦
You're all right.
宝贝 晚餐才刚...
Sweetie, the dinner's just gonna...
晚餐没事儿啦
The dinner's fine.
好
Okay.
快了 快到了...
Almost, almost...
现在...
now...
睁眼！
now!
哦 这是...
Oh, it's ...
好看吗？
-ls that beautiful?
-Oh, it's ...
-Huh?
它太酷炫了
-lt's lovely.
我知道 我在意大利时从一场扑克游戏中赢的
l know. l won it in a poker game in ltaly.
-Huh? -Well...
好吧 开着它小心点 宝贝
well, drive it carefully, honey.
我会的
l will.
享它吧 -我会的
-Enjoy it... -l will.
但要小心
but be careful.
天啊 妈 你真好
God, Ma, you're such a mom.
你准备好了吗 我们去兜风吧
You ready?We're going for a ride.
哦 不 不
Oh, no, no.
我得去做晚饭了
l have to finish dinner.
妈 妈 上来吧
Ma, Ma, one ride.
Oh. Oh...
看啊 妈 我不用手扶
Watch this, Ma, no hands.
噢 弗兰克 别那样做！
Oh, Frank, don't do that!
我不会那样做啦拜托
l wouldn't do that. Come on.
你啊
You!
我押五
l'm in for five.
谢谢你 绅士
Thank you, gentlemen.
我的荣幸
My pleasure.
嘿 妹子 上车吧
Hey, girl. Get in here.
Whoa!
-Oh!
-Whoa!
有趣吧 对吗
This is fun, right?
或许吧
Maybe.
是啊
Yeah.
-哦 小心点 -我开没事儿的
-Ooh, careful. -Hey, l'm driving here.
我回家了
l'm home.
Whoo!
迫击炮来了！迫击炮打来了！
Mortar's coming! Mortar's coming in!
机枪守右侧！机枪守右侧！
Machine gun, right flank! Machine gun, right flank!
军医！
Medic!
这是你看到的过程 对吗
That's when you saw them, huh?
好吧 它运转了
Well, it works.
我的斯派克成功了
My Spike works.
好 好
Okay. Okay.
放轻松
Easy, easy.
好
Okay.
放轻松
-Take it easy.-Take it easy.
不！
No!
妈！
Ma!
你不知道
You don't know
你把你自己弄哪儿来了 兄弟
what it is you got yourself into, bud,
但你现在离家很远
but you're a long way from home.
好奇怪
Oh, but it's so confusing.
到哪儿去 到哪儿去
Where to go,where to go... yes...
妈！
Ma!
哦 烦死了
Oh, bother.
你们是什么鬼东西？
What the hell are you?
他们是涂鸦
They're doodles.
卡通吗？
Cartoons?
别靠太近 博士
Don't get too close, Doc.
我不敢相信我做了什么
l can't believe what l've done.
我的斯派克本该把我送到你的世界里
My Spike was supposed to send me to your world,
而不是你到这儿来
but instead you're here.
这个人不危险
This man's not dangerous to anyone.
至于我们 孩子 我们目前对你来说还不是真的...
As for us, son, we may not be real to you as yet...
但是我们会变成真的
...but we will be.
你现在来到了一个全新的世界
You've come to a whole new world.
你做了一件非常非常不寻常的事情
You've done something extremely rare.
你看 你在一个叫做
You see,you're in a real place
幻世空间的地方
called the Cool World.
Hmm.
哦 怕生啊
Oh. How strange.
说“啊”
Say " ah."
啊
Ah.
But when it comes to making the trip in the body...
你听说建造工作室
Did you hear about the wolf
的狼吗
that built the studio?
不 没有 -我以前从没见过
-No, not...-...l've never seen it before.
Oh!
哦我的妈呀
Oh, my goodness.
对于你妈妈的事很抱歉
l'm sorry about your mother.
你是卡通啊
You're cartoons.
你又不是真的
You're not real.
吼吼 我们是真的 好吗
Oh-ho, we're real, all right.
我已经对里世界旅行的可能性
The possibility of interworld travel
痴迷了很多很多年了
has been an obsession of mine for many, many years.
吼吼吼吼吼
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
嘿 博士 等等
Hey, Doc, wait.
这个人不是你的
This man is not for you.
他又没有治安问题
He's not a police problem.
他是一个科学的秘密
He's a mystery of science.
一个将启的英雄
And a hero to boot.
我才不是英雄
l ain't no hero.
噢 别那么肯定 朋友
Oh, don't be so sure, friend.
打开那个洞之后
With this hole l've opened,
会有各种问题等着呢 哈哈
there could be all kinds of problems. Ha-ha.
他们叫我胡子博士
They call me Doc Whiskers.
你叫什么名字 孩子
What's your name, son?
我叫弗兰克・哈里斯
l'm Frank Harris.
你在你的世界里是做什么的
What did you do in your world?
我以前是个士兵
l was a soldier.
当我走了以后你在这里会很有用的
Oh, you could be useful here when l'm gone.
你从哪来？
Where are you from?
呃 维加斯
Um, Vegas.
明天我们就离开这儿
Tomorrow we're out of here.
虽然你只是幅画 霍莉
You're just a drawing, Holli,
但是我不能没有你
but without you,l'd never have made it.
你今晚看起来真美 宝贝
Oh, you look good tonight, babe.
是时候你来我这里了 杰克
lt's time you came to me, Jack.
来我这儿
Come to me.
哦宝贝儿！
Ooh, baby!
嘿呀嘿呀 嘿呀嘿呀
-Hey-ya, hey-ya.-Hey-ya, hey-ya.
我一直在等你 亲爱的
l've been waiting for you,darlin'
哈？-嗯？
-Huh?-Hmm?
呃  史派奇 你要去做什么 哈？
Uh, Sparky uh, whatcha up to, huh?
你觉得我会告诉
What makes you think
你这种没用的东西吗？
l'd tell a little punk like you?
Why, he's going soft for that tomato.
她叫啥啥啥名字？
Uh... w-w-what's her name?
霍霍霍莉吧 对
H-H-Holli or something. Yeah.
你够了 小兔子
Enough out of you, kitty.
你想妹子还太年轻了点
You're too young to be thinking about girls.
尤其是那个女孩
Especially that girl.
这儿
Here.
给你们点儿木质镍币
A bunch of wooden nickels.
别在一个地方花完了
Don't spend them all in one place.
什什什么？
W-W-What?
飞利浦昨晚逃跑了
Philip flew the coop last night.
嘿 莫丽娜！嘿 莫丽娜！
Hey, Molina! Hey, Molina!
来这儿
Come over here.
你进去了吗
Did you step in it?
嘿 你头上有朵花
Hey, there's a flower on your head.
有很多...
There's are lots of...
嘿
Hey.
小心！
Look out!
我讨厌她见别的男人不告诉我
l hate it when she meets guys without tellin' me.